# **Dhairyasheel Shinge**

**Phone:** +91-9844890900

Actively seeking opportunities to challenge and bring out the best in me!

Email: dshinge87@gmail.com

Starmark Software Pvt. Ltd, 3<sup>rd</sup> floor "Wings", #16/1 Cambridge Road, Halasuru, Bangalore – 560008.

# **Objective**

A dynamic and talented professional with over 5.8 years of experience in Research and Information Technology. Seeking roles in Project Management, Analytics, Software Development, Business Analysis, Client Relationship Management and Operations.

Looking for a full time position in an environment that offers a greater challenge, increased benefits for my family and the opportunity to help the organization advance efficiently and productively.

## **Experience**

#### CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER

Starmark Software Pvt. Ltd, Bengaluru India |

AUG 2020 - Present

➤ Client Management and IT application Consulting

## SENIOR CONFIGURATION ANALYST

Cerner Corporation, Bengaluru, India |

DEC 2015 - JUL 2019 (3.7 years)

- $\blacktriangleright \ \ Required logging, tracking, troubleshooting and escalating results during Configuration$
- Making recommendations to the Clients on design changes and processes
- Client relationship management between internal and external stakeholders
- > Assisted the leadership with facilitation programs and developed training plans

## ASSOCIATE RESEARCH OFFICER

Christian Medical College, Vellore, India

SEP 2013 - SEP 2015 (2 years)

- Research and Development
- Managed a team of 4 on several NIH and CDC sponsored projects related to Virology
- > Involved performing experiments, documenting results and writing papers

## **Education**

Masters of Science | JUL 2011 - AUG 2013

VIT University, Vellore, India

Major: Biotechnology CGPA: 8.74/10

Bachelors of Science | JUN 2007 - OCT 2010

Spicer College, University of Pune, Pune, India.

Major: Biotechnology CGPA: 59%

#### TRAININGS AND CERTIFICATIONS

Management Development Program on "Quantitative and Qualitative Data Analytics using R." – August 2020

Organized by the Indian Institute of Health Management Research University, Jaipur, India.

## **Abilities**

Research Techniques – ELISA, Cell Culture, Virus Purification and Real time PCR experience

Research Tools: SPSS, Internet Explorer, Microsoft Edge, Google Advanced Search,

Office Application: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, OneNote

Other Skills – US Revenue Cycle, Charge Services, ICD-10, HIPAA, Project Management, Client Relationships, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, JIRA, SAS and SOL.

## **Achievements**

VIT ALUMNI Award – Oct 2019 VIT University, Vellore, India

**HIGH FIVE Award -** Sep 2018 Cerner Corporation, Bengaluru

**PROJECT EAGLE Award** – Nov 2017 Cerner Corporation, Bengaluru

RISING STAR Award – Feb 2017 Cerner Corporation, Bengaluru

NOTT Award – Jan 2017 Cerner Corporation, Bengaluru

### References

Will gladly furnish personal and professional references on request.